Guide to the New York Metro Area Postal Union Photographs PHOTOS.011
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series XI: Conventions/Conferences, D; 455574 (Box 2)
  - Convention, New Orleans, undated; 455584
  - New York State Convention, NPU, undated; 455583
- Series XII: Boards/Committees/Councils, V; 455556 (Box 2)
  - MB Advise Conditions- Reg Eng Meeting- 6/1958, Jun 1958; 455572
  - Board Officers meeting w/ Council- 6/12/59 (or 1/1959), Jun 12, 1959; 455571
  - Credit Union Officers- 1959, 455570
  - Credit Union Directors meeting, Executive Board meeting- 1/11/1960, Jan 11, 1960; 455569
  - M Biller Task Force- 9/1961, Sep 1961; 455568
  - Postal Council- 2/1962, Feb 1962; 455567
  - Metro Postal Council- 1/1962, Jan 1962; 455566
  - Metro Postal Council- 1965, 455565
  - Mail Handlers Council (National)- 6/1969, Jun 1969; 455564
  - Board of Officers- 1970, 455563
  - NPU National Automation Committee at Washington, DC- 5/1965, May 1965; 455562
  - NPU National Automation Committee, Detroit Michigan, undated; 455561
  - National Executive Board- 1958-1961, 455560
  - National Board, Washington, DC- 1960, 455559
  - Metro Area Bargaining Council petitions NLRB second region for certification election, undated; 455558
  - Executive Board, NPU, undated; 455557
- Series XIII: Women's Auxiliary, VI; 455548 (Box 2)
  - Ladies' Auxiliary, Manhattan-Bronx Postal Union N Frankfort, undated; 455555
  - Women's Auxiliary Installation- 1961, 455554
  - Women's Auxiliary Installation- 4/1963, Apr 1963; 455553
  - Women's Auxiliary- 1963, 455552
  - Women's Auxiliary luncheon for N Franfort- 1963, 455551
  - Ladies' Auxiliary- 1965, 455550
  - Annual Installation of Officers, Ladies' Auxiliary, Local 10, National Federation of Post Office Clerks, undated; 455549
- Series XIV: Demonstrations/Rallies, VII; 455503 (Box 2)
  - Legislative Rally, Washington, DC- 1957, 455547
  - Pay Raise Rally, Central Commercial HS- 3/24/1957, Mar 24, 1957; 455546
  - Pay Raise Postcard to President-1959, 455545
  - Legislative Rally, Washington, DC- 3/1960, Mar 1960; 455544
  - Legislative Rally, Washington, DC- 6/1961, Jun 1961; 455543
  - Legislative Rally, Washington, DC- 8/1961, Aug 1961; 455542
  - Legislative Rally- 3/1962, May 1962; 455541
  - Washington Pay Rally- 11/ 6-7/1962, Nov 6, 1962 - Nov 7, 1962; 455540
  - Washington Pay Rally- 11/6-7/1962, Nov 6, 1962 - Nov 7, 1962; 455539
  - WMS Rally, New York and Washington, DC- 1963, 455538
  - Rally- 1963, 455537
  - Rally- 5/1963, May-63; 455536
  - Freedom March- 8/28/1963, Aug 28, 1963; 455535
  - Pay Demo- 3/1964, May-64; 455534
  - Demo Met Area Council- 1965, 455533
  - Anti-POMSIP Rally- 1966, 455532
  - Pay rally station demo- 1967 [peanut campaign], 455531
  - Rockefeller Center Station demo- 1967, 455530
  - Poor Peoples March- 1968, 455529
  - Democratic Party Rally- 4/19/69, Apr 19, 1968; 455528
  - Washington Rally- 1969, 455527
  - Peanuts Legislative Program- 1969, 455526
  - Legislative Rally (Pay Raise)- 1969, 455525
  - Pay Raise Rally, Washington, DC- 5/1969 [peanut campaign], May 1969; 455524
  - ACRMD Kids- 5/1969, May 1969; 455523
  - Demonstration supporting HR 13000 (US Aid Bill) Raises for postal employees, Washington, DC- 1969, 455522
  - Pay Raise Demo- General Post Office- 1970, 455521
  - Strike- 1970, 455520
  - Pay Raise Rally- New York City, undated; 455518
- Series XV: Signs/Billboards, VIII; 455502 (Box 3)
  - Union Sign- 1960, 455508
  - Billboards- 1962, 455507
  - Pony Express sign on wall of Union building- 1961, 455506
  - Horse and Buggy Leg Sign, undated; 455505
  - APWU Posters, undated; 455504
- Series XVI: Elections, IX; 455497 (Box 3)
  - Employees rep election- 1962, 455501
  - Employees rep election- 1957, 455500
  - M-H Election- 1964, 455499
  - Mail Handler election, Morgan Station- 1967, 455498
- Series XVII: Contracts, X; 455493 (Box 3)
  - First contract negotiations, Manhattan and Bronx- 1963, 455496
  - First contract Adoption, undated; 455495
  - MH contract signing- 1968, 455494
- Series XVIII: Dinners/Parties, XI; 455462 (Box 3)
  - Annual Children's Christmas Party- 1957, 455492
  - Christmas/ Chanukah Party- 1957, 455491
  - Christmas/ Chanukah Party- 1958, 455490
  - Christmas/ Chanukah Party- 1959, 455489
  - Christmas/ Chanukah Party- 1960, 455488
  - Open House Manhattan-Bronx Postal Union- 6/ 1961, Jun 1961; 455487
  - Annual Delegates Dinner- 1961, 455486
  - Installation Manhattan-Bronx Postal Union- 1961, 455485
  - Installation Manhattan-Bronx Postal Union- 1962, 455484
  - Delegates Dinner- 1962, 455483
  - Delegates Dinner, Diplomat Hotel- 1/1963, Jan 1963; 455482
  - Lincoln Day Dinner, undated; 455481
  - Delegates Dinner- 1/9/1964, Jan 9, 1964; 455480
  - Lincoln Day Dinner- 1964, 455479
  - Cocktail Party- 10/21/1964, Oct 21, 1964; 455478
  - Manhattan-Bronx Postal Union Installation- 1964, 455477
  - Dinner Honoring Cong Ryan- 1964, May 17, 1905; 455476
  - Annual Elardo Award Dinner- 1965, 455475
  - Congressional Breakfast- 1965, May 18, 1905; 455474
  - Open House- New Office- 1/1968, Jan 1968; 455473
  - Inauguration Manhattan-Bronx Postal Union officers- 1968, 455472
  - M Biller, JFK Libraries (Luncheon) Presentation- 1968, 455471
  - Delegates Dinner, Awards- 1/1969, Jan 1969; 455470
  - Biller Testimonial- 1969, 455469
  - B Schwartz Photos NPU Open House, 10th Anniversary NPU- 1969, 455468
  - Delegates Dinner- 1970, 455467
  - Elardo Delegates Dinner- 1972, 455466
  - Annual Dinner, undated; 455465
  - Children's Party [per-1959?], undated; 455464
  - H Kamish Retirement, undated; 455463
- Series XIX: Award Ceremonies, XII; 455435 (Box 3)
  - Membership Prize Winners- 11/1959, 12/1959, Nov 1959 - Dec 1959; 455461
  - Presentation of Scroll by Joint Conference to David Silvergleid- 1/1960, Jan 1960; 455460
  - Membership Prize Winners- 2/17/1960, Feb 17, 1960; 455459
  - Cong Addabbo receiving Elardo Award- 1963, 455458
  - Scholarship Award- 1964, 455457
  - Elardo Dinner- 1964, 455456
  - Elardo Presentation, undated; 455455
  - Scholarship Board- 1965, 455454
  - NYPO Art Awards- 1965, 455453
  - NYPO Art Winners- 1967, 455452
  - Turkey Winners- 1967/ Meeting- 1963, 455451
  - Goltz Scholarship Award- 1968, 455450
  - NYPO Prize Winner Photo- 8/1969, Aug 1969; 455449
  - Handicap Winner- 1969, 455448
  - Scholastic Winners- 1969, 455447
  - Elardo Family- 1/1970, Jan 1970; 455446
  - Elardo Family, undated; 455445
  - Scholarship Award, undated; 455444
  - World Fair Tix Raffle, undated; 455443
  - Post Master General J Lapenta receiving Elardo Award, undated; 455442
- Series XX: Classes/Seminars, XIII; 455434 (Box 3)
  - Harry Kamish Fed Workshop- 1947-48, 1947-1948; 455441
  - Sen Javits and Pres MacKay Labor Studies College Teacher Training Institute-1961, 455440
  - Seminar at New School, undated; 455439
  - Delegates Seminars- 1968, 455438
  - Delegates Seminar, Union Office, undated; 455437
  - Community Classes- 1/1970, Jan 1970; 455436
- Series XXI: Workplaces, XIV; 455407 (Box 3)
  - Brooklyn Army Terminal (BAT)- 3/1969, Mar 1969; 455433
  - Job-Mobile, Strahn Post Master- 1968, 455432
  - M-H on Job Training, undated; 455431
  - MVO- Pictures- 1969, 455430
  - Checking air pollution, work floor- 1964, 455429
  - Worksites, Miscellaneous, undated; 455428
  - Stations- 1969, 455427
- Series XXII: Union Office Staff, XV; 455392 (Box 3)
  - J Ecker, Fin Sec and M Kanner, Sec, undated; 455406
  - Office Staff- 10/1959, Oct 1959; 455405
  - Union Offices- 12/1959, Dec 1959; 455404
  - Union at work- 12/1959, Dec 1959; 455403
  - Union Office- 3/1963, Mar 1963; 455402
  - Credit Union Office- 1965, 455401
  - Membership campaign- 1966, 455400
  - General Post Office Staff Retirees- 10/1969, Oct 1969; 455399
  - Checking 1187's, undated; 455398
  - M-B Office, undated; 455397
  - Office Staff: L Mitchell, undated; 455396
  - Maintenance, undated; 455395
  - NPU Health Plan, undated; 455394
  - Morley Kantor, undated; 455393
- Series XXIII: The Union Mail, XVI; 455386 (Box 3)
  - Union Mail editor- Mgr editor- 1959, 455391
  - Editors Union Mail- 1967, 455390
  - Editing Union Mail- 1969, 455389
  - M Kanner, Union Mail, undated; 455388
  - Turkeys (Cartoon), undated; 455387
- Series XXIV: Sports/Recreation, XVII; 455377 (Box 3)
  Arranged by sport and then chronologically.
  - Subseries A: Baseball, 464476
    - Baseball Champs- Morgan Station Team, Chelsea Park- 1963, 455700
    - Baseball Team- 1965 [see also Series 17-B: Folder 2 Softball Team-1965"], 455699
    - Baseball Tournament, Chelsea Park- 1964 [see also Series 17-B: Folder 2 Softball Team-1965"], 455698
    - Miscellaneous Baseball, undated; 455697
  - Subseries B: Softball, 464477
    - Softball Champs- 1963, 455644
    - Softball Team- 1965 [see also Series 17-A: Folder 2 Baseball Team- 1965"], 455643
    - Softball Champs- 1965 [see also Series 17-A: Folder 4 Miscellaneous Baseball], 455642
    - Opening Game Softball- 1968, 455641
    - Softball Champs- 1969, 455640
  - Subseries C: Basketball, 464478
    - Basketball Champs- 6/1964, Jun 1964; 455612
    - Basketball- 1964, 455611
    - Basketball- 1965, 455610
  - Subseries D: Bowling, 464479
    - Bowling- 1956, 455582
    - Bowling Season- 1957-58, 1957-1958; 455581
    - Bowling League Champs- 1958, 455580
    - Bowling Winners- 12/1959, Dec 1959; 455579
    - Bowling Season- 1963-64 (or 1965-66), 1963-1964; 455578
    - Bowling- 1964, 455577
    - Bowling, Madison Square- 1967-68, 1967-1968; 455576
    - Bowling- 1969-70, 1969-1970; 455575
  - Subseries E: Chess, E; 455384
    - Chess Club, M Siderman, VPGPO- 6/1963, Jun 1963; 455385
  - Subseries F: Handball, F; 455381
    - Handball Tourney- 6/1963, Jun 1963; 455383
    - Handball Champ, undated; 455382
  - Subseries G: Miscellaneous, G; 455378
    - Sports Awards- 7/1961, 455380
    - Sports Director W Boone, undated; 455379
- Series XXV: National Federation of Postal Clerks--Local 10 (New York), XVIII; 455376 (Box 3)
  - National Federation of Postal Clerks- Local 10 (New York)- Events (ca 1953-1959), 455696
  - Natl Fed of Postal Clerks- Local 10 (New York)-Portraits-Identified-Alphabetical, undated; 455639
  - Natl Fed Of Postal Clerks-Local 10 (New York)-Portraits-Unidentified, undated; 455638
- Series XXVI: Miscellaneous, XIV; 455375 (Box 3)
  - Co-op City, Bronx- 11/1968, Nov 1968; 455426
  - Dolls in Hospital- 1959, 455425
  - General Post Office Fire- 1966, 455424
  - FDR Post office, model of proposed building, undated; 455423
  - Freedom National Bank, undated; 455422
  - Fowler, Rom (children) [see Series 19 Miscellaneous Negs], undated; 455421
  - Inquiring Editor, undated; 455420
  - Morgan Fire, undated; 455419
  - Union Recognition- 11/ 1961, Nov 1961; 455418
  - Misc, 1958, 455417
  - Misc, Identified, undated; 455416
  - Misc, Unidentified, undated; 455415
  - Misc, Unidentified, undated; 455414
  - A Ryland, E Bailey, undated; 455413
  - Negatives (ca 1970s) without matching contact sheets in the collection, 1970-1979; 455412
  - Miscellaneous contact sheets (ca1970s) possibly with matching negatives [see Series 19: Folder 17 Miscellaneous negatives, possibly with matching contact sheets], 1970-1979; 455411
  - Miscellaneous negatives (ca 1970s) that may have matching contact sheets in the collection (see Series 19: Folder 16, 1970-1979; 455410
  - Contact sheets (ca 1970s) that have matching negatives in the collection (Matching negatives may be found in Series 19, Folder 19: Miscellaneous negatives that have matching contact sheets in the collection), 1970-1979; 455409
  - Miscellaneous negatives (ca 1970s) that have matching contact sheets in the collection (Matching contact sheets may be found in Series 19, Folder 18: Miscellaneous contact sheets that have matching negatives in the collection), 1970-1979; 455408